pokerstarsblog.com 2010-06-17

# Poker Stars - Online Poker Software Privacy Policy - Privacy Issues

Your privacy on the Internet is very important to PokerStars and its owner and operator, Rational Entertainment Enterprises Limited. We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of the personal information collected by us in order to allow you to enjoy playing poker online at PokerStars, by safeguarding it utilizing the best in class software and hardware architecture, techniques, methods and procedures.

The purpose of this privacy policy is to enable you to understand how we collect, store, use and safeguard information relating to you and for you to understand your rights in relation to that information.

1\. What information is collected and for what purpose

As part of the PokerStars Account Opening process, we will ask you to provide us with certain personal information, including a name, postal address, e-mail address and password as well as to certify that you are at least 18 years old or older in jurisdictions in which the minimum age for use of the PokerStars services is greater than 18. We will use your personal information to confirm various financial transactions, to occasionally send you events and news information and to provide you with customer support services. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter. The name you register with must be yours. In addition, it is very important that you complete the account details with valid information, since they will be used in the course of validating financial transactions and the other aforementioned purposes.

Players are able to change account details by selecting an Account option in the downloaded software.

2\. Deposit and withdrawal processing

To play for real money, Players will need to make a deposit. In the course of making a deposit, Players will need to provide deposit method information (example: credit card number). This information in conjunction with your other personal information might be used to clear financial transactions executed by you with PokerStars.

3\. Confidentiality

PokerStars undertakes substantial efforts to protect the confidentiality of the identity, preferences and other information it has collected about individual Players and will not knowingly allow access to this information to anyone outside PokerStars, other than to the Player or as described in this Privacy Policy. PokerStars has made a substantial investment in its server, database, backup, firewall and encryption technologies to protect the information collected by PokerStars. These technologies are deployed as part of state of the art security architecture, see [www.pokerstars.com/poker/room/features/security/](http://www.pokerstars.com/poker/room/features/security/).

All PokerStars employees are required to comply with the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy provides that employees are obligated to keep Player information strictly confidential. This obligation continues once an employee has left our Company.

You should also do your part in protecting your information. Your PokerStars Player password is confidential and we recommend that you not divulge it to anyone or enable others to discover it.

4\. Limits of Confidentiality

Legally Required Disclosures: Due to the existing legal, regulatory and security environment, PokerStars may be required, under certain circumstances, to disclose personally identifiable information about our Players. PokerStars will use its best reasonable efforts to limit such disclosure to the following: where PokerStars believes in good faith that it is required to do so in response to a subpoena, warrant or other legal process; or where reasonably necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities to preserve and/or enforce PokerStars' rights. Further, we can, and you authorize us to, disclose your Player identification, name, street address, city, state, post code, country, phone number, e-mail, and company to third party agents of PokerStars as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy or other unlawful activity or activity that may expose us to legal liability.

5\. Who receives your information?

In addition to legally required disclosures as explained in Section 4 above, we may disclose your personal information to our employees, employees of other companies related to or affiliated with Rational Entertainment Enterprises Limited and to third party service providers who use your personal information to provide services to us in respect of your being a Player with PokerStars. All recipients of your personal information shall be bound by applicable data protection laws to keep your personal information private at no less a level than that by which we are bound.

6\. Your rights in relation to your information

We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. You can write to us at any time to review, change, obtain a copy of your information or have your details altered or corrected in accordance with your rights under the Data Protection Act 2002. In order to contact us regarding your information please e-mail [support@pokerstars.com](mailto:support@pokerstars.com). We may in certain circumstances levy a small charge to cover the cost of administration regarding any request made by you in this regard.

7\. Cookies

We may send you a temporary cookie when you visit [www.PokerStars.com](http://www.pokerstars.com/) website. A cookie is a text-only string of information that we place in your computer's cookie file so that we can remember who you are when you revisit [www.PokerStars.com](http://www.pokerstars.com/) website. We may use the data generated from cookies to compile statistical data on your use of our website. You are not obliged to accept the cookie from us and you have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. Please see [www.cookiecentral.com/faq](http://www.cookiecentral.com/faq) if you require any further information about the placing, use or deletion of cookies.

8\. Consent to Privacy Policy

By opening an Account with PokerStars, you agree to the terms of this PRIVACY POLICY. We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy and encourage you to periodically review it. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page. Your continued use of the PokerStars services constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates. Our [Terms of Service](http://www.pokerstars.com/poker/room/tos/), see [www.pokerstars.com/poker/room/tos](http://www.pokerstars.com/poker/room/tos/), take precedence over any conflicting provision of this Privacy Policy.

9\. Who are we?

Rational Entertainment Enterprises Limited  
33-37 Athol Street  
Douglas  
Isle of Man, IM1 1LB  

Privacy Policy last revised: 02 June, 2008

Back to top
